gatheringguide.com 2015-11-18

# Privacy Policy - Gathering Guide

  |  **Information We Collect**

  We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out various online forms.  

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  

**Use of Information**

  Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:    
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  

To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  

To process transactions We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes without your consent.  

To send periodic emails The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to an order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  

    **Protection of User Information**

  We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order  

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  

Your private information (credit cards information) is transmitted directly to our Payment gateway provider and is not stored on our servers.  

**Cookies**

  Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information  

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.  

**Information Disclosure**

  We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

**Third party links**

  Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  

**Vendors**

  Businesses that choose to have an online profile on the GatheringGuide.com may not opt-out of receiving certain emails.  

  **Terms and Conditions**

  Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.gatheringguide.com/cp/terms  

**Your Consent**

  By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.  

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  

This policy was last modified on 6/1/2013  

|
